

g.foozxteraex@gmail.com
(123) 456 78 99
Alabama

www.qwikresume.com

Professional Summary

7+ years of experience as a Software Developer, expertise in application design, development, deployment, implementation, testing and maintenance of Enterprise and Web applications. Extensive SDLC experience including requirement analysis, design, coding, application implementation, unit testing, system testing, documentation and production support.

Work Experience

Software Developer II

ABC Corporation Jan / 2019 - Ongoing Jersey City, NJ

- NJ managerial controls/ observation hub managerial controls is an application that helps managers of a team monitor their clients to make sure they interacted within a timely manner.
- Observation hub is an application where positive or anomalous observations of various teams are recorded.
- Direct interaction with the different team managers to document their needs and requirements for the application.

Software Developer

ABC Corporation Jan / 2019 - Ongoing Washington, DC

- Agility harmony is the new email marketing platform built from scratch to replace epsilon's legacy software dream and dream mail.
- The target of this software is to create an email campaign to send billions of emails on the behalf of its client such as chase, Citi bank, Macy's, toys r us, Marriott, etc.
- This software also keeps track of the reporting metrics such as the number of emails delivered, clicked, opened and link redirects for billing the clients.

Education

Bachelor Of Engineering in Electronics

Tribhuvan University - Kathmandu Jan / 2019 - Ongoing New York

B.E.

SRM University Jan / 2019 - Ongoing Location

HS

Board/University Jan / 2019 - Ongoing Location

Skills			
Core Java	J2EE	JSP	Servlets

Achievements

Award

Achievements can be used in resumes, job applications, and professional profiles to demonstrate skills, experience, and accomplishments.